

CRISTIANA VIEIRA

DEGREE IN MARKETING AND ADVERTISING

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hi, my name is Cristiana, I'm 22 years old and I consider myself an organized, committed, empathetic and communicative person. I'm always looking for continuous improvement and personal development with focus on my goals and aiming to achieve good results. I'm motivated to continue self developing on either my personal and professional perspectives.

CONTACTS

- Rua Monte Alto, 316 Rebordosa-Paredes Porto, Portugal
- cristiana.marketeer@gmail.com
- 910 25 45 70
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/cristia navieira2403/
- https://www.instagram.com/crisfnvieira/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

February 2022- May 2022

Up We Go- Digital Marketing Agency, Porto

Management of Social Networks like Facebook, LinkedIn and Instagram (Swonkie and Meta Business Suite)

Content Writing (Blog Posts, Websites, Posts For Social Networks, Magazines, Ebooks, Brochures, Formal Documents For Clients)
Competition Analysis

Benchmarking

Usability Tests (Mobile & Desktop)

Implementation Of Content On The Website (WordPress)

Newsletters funcionality tests

MARKETING ASSISTANT- INTERN

19 VALUES.

August 2018- August 2019
O Meu Sorriso Clínicas
DENTAL ASSISTANT- FULL TIME JOB

April 2018 - June 2018

Trofa Saúde - Hospital Privado de Alfena

Assistant in the health area in many specialties:

Obstetrics/gynecology, ophthalmology, otolaryngology, speech therapy, occupational therapy, child psychology, child and adolescent psychiatry, medical oncology, examination rooms and polysomnography rooms.

HEALTHCARE ASSISTANT AT EXTERN CONSULTATIONS-INTERN

18 VALUES.

May 2017 - June 2017 Lar São Lourenço, Ermesinde HEALTHCARE ASSISTANT - INTERN 18 VALUES.

HOBBIES

- Travel
- Sport
- Photography
- Films
- Music
- Read magazines and blogs from different areas
- Do online courses
- Participate in Workshops

EDUCATION

Degree in Marketing and Advertising

ISCET, Instituto Superior de Ciências Empresariais e do Turismo 2019-2022

Grade: 16

Health Assistant- Level 4 Professional Course

Escola Profissional de Valongo

2015-2018

Final project: 20 Values Final grade: 17 Values

CERTIFICATES

- Digital Marketing Google Atelier Digital
- Social Media Management- Elife & BuzzMonitor
- Google Analytics for Beginners Google Analytics Academy
- Copywriting for conversions: How to Write Persuasive Content - Alison
- Inbound Marketing HubSpot Academy
- Creative Writing and Storytelling for Local Businesses Maia City Council and Rural Coast
- Emotional Photography for Business Maia City Council and Rural Coast
- Creative Photography for Local Businesses Maia City Council and Rural Coast
- Introduction to Digital Marketing for Businesses Mentor Maria Gonçalves

LANGUAGES

- · Portuguese Native Language
- English Intermediate

SKILLS

- · Good interpersonal relationships
- Good presentation and diction
- · Good interaction and communication skills
- · Good ability to work in a group
- · Good capacity for autonomy and personal organization
- · Good time management skills
- · Ability to work under pressure
- · Problem solving ability
- Mastery of Office, Canva, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Asana, Swonkie, Etus, Miro, GoVisually, Wordpress and Meta Business Suite

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

2012: Dancer

2015: Handball player

2016-2018: Swimmer and gym workout

2019-2022: Delegate of the 1st, 2nd and 3rd year of the Degree in

Marketing and Advertising

2021 and 2022: Representative member of the Degree in Marketing and Advertising at the Pedagogical Council of ISCET

2021: Publication of the article "Artificial intelligence and the impact on marketing and the consumer" in the Scientific Journal of ISCET Percursos & Ideias n°11 - 2nd series 2021

2022: Article with finished writing "The impact of influencers on the transition from fast fashion to slow fashion" in the subject "Research Project"